Have you ever been?
来たことある?
here.
ここ
It's my first time here.
初めて来ました
It's spacious, isn't it?
広いでしょ
Surprised.
びっくり
I thought there would be fewer people.
もっと人少ないと思ってたから
cute.
かわいい
Bears are good.
くまがいい
Ah, I like pigs.
あ、豚がいい
Is it cute?
かわいいの?
this.
これ
do.
やる
I'll do this.
これやる
Anpanman.
アンパンマンや
He's a child.
子供やな
This is cute.
これはかわいい
I'm sorry.
すいませんしな
welcome.
いらっしゃいませ
please.
お願いします
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I'll put it in.
入れておきます
It's true.
本当だ
cute.
かわいい
please wait a moment.
少々お待ちください
It's hard to breathe.
息苦しいよね
息苦しい
I'm tired.
疲れたよ
Tired.
疲れる
I'm tired.
疲れてる
Okay.
よ いしょ
cute.
かわいい
Oh, really?
あ、ほんと?
Tired?
疲れる?
With the person in front of me.
前の人と
On the left side.
左寄りで
Here, a white man, a girl,
ここにさ、 白いおじさん、 少女でさ、
I want to fall in love.
恋をしたい
I miss you.
寂しいね
Oh, sorry.
あ、すいません
Sorry.
すいません
Is something not moving?
何か動いてない?
amazing.
すごい
I'm going to use it.
ぶ つかっちゃう
We'll collide.
ぶつかっちゃう
This way, this way.
こっちこっち
Let's go in the same direction.
同じ方に行こう
It's true.
本当だ
We're together.
一緒や
tired.
疲れた
It's something like that.
何かあれだね
Collide.
ぶつかる
There are people.
人がいる
Right now.
今ね
Collide.
ぶつかる
Because I can see it.
だって見える
Oh, I'm heading this way.
あ、こっち向いちゃった
It's true.
本当だ
Can you see that from the other side?
向こうからあっち見えるのかな?
I can see it.
見えるよ
It was here, it was here.
ここでした、ここでした
It would be nice to play.
遊んだらいいね
this.
これ
I'll make a big one.
大きいのは作る
difficult.
難しい
If you blow the wind slowly, it will be big.
ゆっくり風をしたら大きいんだよね
fun.
楽しい
close.
近 い
近い
close.
It's so cold.
めっちゃ寒い
be seen by people.
人に見られる
Can be seen.
見られる
There are a lot of people.
いっぱい人おる
Sorry, it was so small.
ごめん、ちいちゃった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Akande.
あかんで
Like this.
こんな
no good.
あかん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can be seen.
見られる
There are a lot of people.
いっぱい人おる
It's scary.
怖いよ
It's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいけど
I got bored.
ちゅうしちゃったよ
I can't see you here.
こっち見られへん
I'm embarrassed.
恥ずかしくて
I'll go somewhere nearby.
近いところ行くよ
let's go.
行こう
I'll do my best, up to that point.
頑張るぞ、あそこまで
Dash, dash.
ダッシュ、ダッシュ
Dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
危ない、危ない、危ない
More difficult than the surrounding carts.
周りのカートより難しい
scared.
怖い
I did it.
しちゃいましたね
Can I take this off?
これ、脱いでいい?
yes.
はい
Did you come with your teacher?
先生と来た?
get nervous.
緊張する
I've only seen it where it's always attached.
いつも付けになるところでしか見たことないしね
It's difficult.
難しいです
Hmm.
うーん
The teacher also made it funny
先生もおかしさ付けしたから
hey.
ね
Oh no!
や ばいよ
I can't go back now.
もう、また戻りにできない
Do you miss sleeping on your own?
自分で寝るの懐かしい?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, let's go to sleep by ourselves.
じゃあ、自分で寝なそう
That's what it means.
そういう意味よね
It's like, just take it off a little bit.
ちょっとだけ脱いでよみたいな
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Scary, Shaki.
怖い、シャキ
Did you expect to see Shaki today?
今日のシャキ、見られると思ってた?
I don't think so.
思ってない
TRUE?
本当?
The one in the front.
一番前にあるやつか
Look, look.
見て、ほら
It's more nostalgic to be seen.
見られるほうが懐かしい
Look, look.
見て、ほら
Is it visible?
映ってる?
It's reflected.
映ってる
Shaki, did you see it?
シャキ、見映っちゃった?
When I was in junior high school, I wore loose clothes like this.
中学生の時、こういうのさ、 フワに着たまま、
I didn't pull my sleeves off or take them off.
袖抜いて、取ったりとかしなかった、
Like when changing clothes for club activities.
部活着替える時とか
I won't.
しないですよ
Why don't you just remove everything?
全部抜いてしないの?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Take off your sleeves and go back to sleep?
袖抜いて、 また寝る?
Should I sleep?
寝るかな?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Did you remove it?
外したのか?
Should I take it off?
外すの?
Take it off.
外すの
Just your hands.
手だけに
I can't see it.
見られへん
Can't see it?
見られない?
Well then, okay.
じゃあ、いいよ
I also like that it looks familiar.
見慣れてるのも好きだから
It doesn't come out.
出てこない
It won't come out.
出てこないよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
Stop it.
やめてよ
Are you sleeping?
寝てる?
This is cute, Panty.
これかわいいね、パンティ
How cute?
かわいくらい?
favorite?
お気に入り?
What's going on in the back?
後ろ、これどうなってんの?
Back, lace.
後ろ、レース
It's Ichi's panties.
イッチのパンティだ
like?
好き?
Hey, Ichi's panties.
ちょっと、イッチのパンティ
cute,
かわいい、
this.
これ
Awesome.
す げえ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Kaa
かっ
Is this okay?
こ いい?
a,
あ、
I put it in.
入 れちゃった
Could you please look at the camera?
カメラのほうを見ててくれない?
What if I bend my elbows?
ひじまげたら?
Isn't it easy?
楽ちいんじゃない?
Yeah.
うん
Do you see me embarrassed?
恥ずかしい姿映ってる?
I got sleepy.
眠くなっちゃった
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Dowa dowa.
ドワドワする
That's a cute pussy.
かわいいおまんこだね
Can I film it?
映していい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
I'm going to turn my skirt around.
スカート回しちゃおうと
How do you do it?
どう やってやるの?
Can you sew it for me?
縫いでくれる?
sew.
縫う
Get serious.
真剣になって
Wow, it's shining.
すごい、光ってます
Doesn't that mean you can sew?
縫えてるってことじゃないんですか?
Ah, Chuichi's ass.
あ、中イッチの尻が
It's frozen.
固まっちゃってるよ
I have a middle-aged butt.
中イッチの尻ついてるよ
How does it feel?
どんな気持ちいい?
Want to hide it?
隠したい?
I want to hide it.
隠したい
Can I lick it?
舐めていい?
cute.
かわいい
Have you been there?
行ったことあるの?
How should I go?
どうやったら行く?
I don't know.
分かんない
Will it work if I assemble it?
組み立てたら行きそう?
Against?
対する?
When has this ever happened?
いつあったことある?
do not have.
ない
not at all.
全然
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Try moving it.
動かしてみて
Dowa dowa.
ドワドワする
What do you mean by your feelings?
自分の気持ちってこと?
I had it done for me.
してもらったんだけど
Are you touching it?
触れてる?
Yeah.
うん
Did you do it?
できた?
Is it done yet?
まだできてる?
Is it done?
できてる?
I'll use it here.
こっちに使っちゃう
Don't have any hands?
手ない?
protect your hand
手をかお
cormorant.
う
Did it feel good?
気 持ちよかった?
Like Chinch again.
チンチのようにまた
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Do you feel good about yourself?
自分の気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
It feels so good because it's so slippery.
すごいヌルヌルだから気持ちいい
Have you never had a favorite day?
好きな日やったことないの?
do not have.
ない
Does it feel good if I do it like this?
このまんまやったら気持ちいい?
Don't you think it feels good?
気持ちいいと思わない?
It feels good.
気持ちいいそう
Will you be angry if I continue like this?
このままやったら怒る?
Yeah.
うん
Aren't you angry?
怒らない?
Yeah.
うん
Can it feel good?
気持ちよいできる?
It's it.
イッチや
Like this.
こうやって
Like a pet.
ペットみたいな
what happened?
どうしたの?
My stomach is growling.
お腹鳴ってる
cute.
かわいい
I got lost again.
またかぐれちゃった
Hey.
ね え
Good.
よいしょ
At the feet of the program.
番組の足で
can?
できる?
Like this.
こうやって
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
You like this, right?
これ好きでしょ?
Open your legs.
足開いて
It's going to be this way.
こっちになっちゃうね
Let's just have some fun.
だいたい楽しもうね
Does Chubby feel good?
ぽっちゃん気持ちいい?
I'm chubby though.
ぽっちゃんだけど
Try opening it.
開いてみて
Show me this.
こっちを見せて
You can just press it.
押すだけるから
Because I couldn't get it out.
抜けなくなっちゃったから
can?
でき る?
This one here too.
こっちもこっちに
child
こ
Is it okay?
わ すのかな?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Try it.
いってみて
Well then, over here.
じゃあ、こっちに
Which one will it be?
どれになる?
Sneak into Kurtolas.
クルトラスにこそって
That's difficult.
難しいね
Have you ever worn white clothes like this?
このまま白服入れたことある?
I wouldn't mind if I made a mistake.
間違えてもしんないだろうね
Is it okay if I get the exemption in 2 days?
2日で省略を受けたらいいかな?
Anywhere?
どこでもいい?
You can't go very far.
あんま遠く行けないよね
In the near future.
近目のところ
let's go.
行こう
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Even if it stops.
止まっても
Punch?
ポンチ?
Your mother called you just now.
お前、さっきお母さんが電話してたよ
Mom's video.
お 母さんの動画
It's probably a lie, right?
多分嘘でしょ?
I fell asleep for a while.
ちょっと眠られちゃったね
I have to go home.
帰らないと
Shall we stop next time?
今度止まろう?
Let's go home early.
早く帰ろう
Please try to go home early.
早く帰ろうとしてください
Let's go home early.
早く帰ろう
Ah, punch.
あー、ポンチ
Yeah.
うん
It's coming up.
上がってきたよ
Can I show my hips?
お腰出してもいい?
Yeah.
うん
Hey, it feels good.
おい、気持ちいい
I want to go home early
早く帰ろうと
Please do so.
して ください
Go to sleep.
寝てよ
Even if I sleep a little.
ちょっと寝ても
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Get medical help.
医療出して
Isn't it bad?
まずくない?
I just forgot about it.
ついとって忘れてた
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I'll come here next time.
今度こっち来るんですよね